[
        {
                "question": "Этот результат впечатлит их?",
                "answer": "Will this result impress them?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я покажу это тебе",
                "answer": "I'll show it to you"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я не покажу тебе этот отчет",
                "answer": "I won't show you this report"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это не принесет тебе больше денег",
                "answer": "It won't bring you more money"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы займем первое место?",
                "answer": "Will we take the first place?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это будет громадный успех?",
                "answer": "Will it be a huge success?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Будет необходимо перевести это на английский",
                "answer": "It'll be necessary to translate it into English"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я постораюсь не говорить это",
                "answer": "I'll try not to say it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я поеду в другое место",
                "answer": "I'll go to another place"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я буду делать это, чтобы зарабатывать больше денег",
                "answer": "I'll do it to earn more money"
        },
        {
                "question": "Почему ты пойдешь в этот ресторан?",
                "answer": "Why will you go to this restaurant?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Почему твои коллеги будут заинтересованы в этом?",
                "answer": "Why will your colleagues be interested in it?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это не обязательно означает, что он выучит английский за год",
                "answer": "It doesn't necessarily mean that he'll learn english in a year"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я знаю, у него будет маленькая зарплата",
                "answer": "I know he'll have a low salary"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я постораюсь не забыть сказать ему эту вещь",
                "answer": "I'll try not to forget to tell him this thing"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я скоро закончу готовиться к этому экзамену",
                "answer": "I'll finish preparing for this exam soon"
        },
        {
                "question": "Кто разрешит этот конфликт?",
                "answer": "Who will resolve this conflict?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Как они себя будут вести?",
                "answer": "How will they behave"
        },
        {
                "question": "Кто скоро уйдет из дома?",
                "answer": "Who will leave home?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Что за причина такого странного ответа?",
                "answer": "What's the reason for such a strange answer?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они скоро разведутся",
                "answer": "They'll get divorced soon"
        },
        {
                "question": "Эти условия подойдут нам",
                "answer": "These conditions suit us"
        },
        {
                "question": "Она сохранит этот секрет",
                "answer": "She'll keep this secret"
        },
        {
                "question": "Ты не выучишь английский за год",
                "answer": "You won't learn english in a year"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они смогут найти это везде",
                "answer": "They'll be able to find it everywhere"
        },
        {
                "question": "Эти новости впечатлят его",
                "answer": "This news will impress him"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы постараемся удвоить наши продажи",
                "answer": "We'll try to double our sales"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я буду гордиться твоими результатами",
                "answer": "I'll be proud of your results"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я сумею удвоить наши продажи несмотря на кризис",
                "answer": "I'll manage to double our sales despite the crisis"
        },
        {
                "question": "Какие фрукты и овощи они будут есть там?",
                "answer": "What fruit and vegetables will they eat there?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они не починят это легко",
                "answer": "They won't repair it easily"
        },
        {
                "question": "Ты потратишь в пустую время и деньги",
                "answer": "You'll waste time and money"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это будет настоящей сенсацией",
                "answer": "It'll be a real sensation"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я постораюсь не обсуждать это",
                "answer": "I'll try not to discuss it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Что нужно будет проверить более тщательно?",
                "answer": "What will be necessary to check more thoroughly"
        },
        {
                "question": "Он сможет купить это очень дешево",
                "answer": "He'll be able to buy it very cheaply"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это будет нашим достижением",
                "answer": "It'll be our achievement"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я думаю, у тебя будет хорошо с иностранными языками",
                "answer": "I think you'll be good at foreign languages"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы выиграем несмотря на наши плохие шансы",
                "answer": "We'll win despite our bad chances"
        },
        {
                "question": "ты услишишь это в начале",
                "answer": "You'll hear it in the beginning"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я начну работать над этой проблемой",
                "answer": "I'll start working on this problem"
        },
        {
                "question": "не обязательно",
                "answer": "Not necessarily"
        },
        {
                "question": "Что за причина этого?",
                "answer": "What's the reason for it?"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я смогу улучшить свой английский значительно",
                "answer": "I'll be able to improve my english significantly"
        },
        {
                "question": "Возможности",
                "answer": "Apportunities"
        },
        {
                "question": "Этот канал поможет вам выучить английский бесплатно",
                "answer": "This channell will help you learn english free"
        },
        {
                "question": "Причина этого",
                "answer": "Reason for it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Вы мне очень помогли",
                "answer": "You helped me a lot"
        },
        {
                "question": "Он позвонил ей снова",
                "answer": "He called her again"
        },
        {
                "question": "Он пытался получить ту работу, но без успеха",
                "answer": "He tried to get that job but without success"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я пользовался интернетом практически каждый день",
                "answer": "I used the internet almost every day"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мне нужно было связаться с ней",
                "answer": "I needed to get in touch with her"
        },
        {
                "question": "Она задала ему пару вопросов",
                "answer": "She asked him a couple of questions"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я часто слушал музыку",
                "answer": "I often listened to music"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это произошло со мной",
                "answer": "It happened to me"
        },
        {
                "question": "Он повернулся и улыбнулся ей",
                "answer": "He turned and smiled at her"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я начал изучать английский два года назад",
                "answer": "I started learning english two years ago"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они жили счастливо",
                "answer": "They loved happily"
        },
        {
                "question": "Он верил ей",
                "answer": "He believed her"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы включили его имя",
                "answer": "We included his name"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я включил свет",
                "answer": "I turned on the light"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я выключил радио (not turn)",
                "answer": "I switched off the radio"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они появились, затем они исчезли",
                "answer": "They appeared and then they disappeared"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они исчезли вдруг",
                "answer": "They disappeared suddenly"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они неожиданно исчезли",
                "answer": "They disappeared unexpectedly"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они предложили пойти в кино",
                "answer": "They suggested going to the cinema"
        },
        {
                "question": "Все осталось таким же",
                "answer": "Everything remained the same"
        },
        {
                "question": "Он остался моим другом",
                "answer": "He remained my friend"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я остался спокойным",
                "answer": "I remained calm"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это развивало наши способности",
                "answer": "It developed our abilities"
        },
        {
                "question": "Мы развивали наши профессиональные навыки",
                "answer": "We developed our professional skills"
        },
        {
                "question": "Это требовало больше усилий",
                "answer": "It required more efforts"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они требовали больше опыта",
                "answer": "They required more experience"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я решил сделать это (пр. вр.)",
                "answer": "I decided to do it"
        },
        {
                "question": "Я получил это письмо",
                "answer": "I received this letter"
        },
        {
                "question": "Они производили очень дорогие товары",
                "answer": "They produced very expensive goods"
        },
        {
                "question": "",
                "answer": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "",
                "answer": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "",
                "answer": ""
        },
        {
                "question": "",
                "answer": ""
        },
]
